so for our next talk we have uh people
who have quite who have come quite from
far away from Brazil and
Portugal uh to talk about property
search and how multimodal LM based
search assistance can improve property
search um yeah we have Tana Julio and
Lucas from Quinto Andor to
give a presentation thank
you uh thank you very much for the
introduction uh there will be as many as
three of us because we were sampling
from from the large team but we will be
disciplined with time don't worry uh my
name is Tana uh I'm head of data science
at kintar uh Julia is Staff data
scientist and Lucas is Staff machine
learning engineer and we will talk about
uh building a multimodel llm based
searches assistant chatboard but uh of
course we have absolutely absolutely
unique internal uh name for this project
we call it copilot
so yes uh and we will uh talk a little
bit about details how we did it so uh we
will put you a little bit into the
context of what our company does explain
uh why we decided to build the assistant
this way and what were the main
components and of course of course uh
what were the Lessons Learned on this uh
very fun uh
Journey uh so uh kintar is one of the
largest uh property tech companies in
Latin America uh we help people to find
houses to leave or to rent and what is
important we provide many useful uh
additional Services uh to do that so for
example we guarantee for the landlord
that tenant will pay the rent on time uh
during all um all the period of the
contract or we allow people schedule uh
visits to the uh places uh online and
reschedule them online sign the
contracts online so I don't know how
good is real estate market in Germany in
Portugal we would love to have the same
services available it would make our
life so much easier
there so uh our headquarter is in San
Paulo Brazil we operate in five more
countries but uh and we have a technical
Hub in
Portugal so in terms of the uh
information retrieval game it's very
interesting because we have million of
people uh visiting our platforms every
month uh million of properties listed so
search is a super nice super great thing
to do sorry I am a bit nervous also I
trained for a long time but uh yeah okay
so uh why copilot uh why this assistant
chatbot um when it comes to the rent in
uh your house ideal experience is not
using filters on site or uh using a free
even not using uh perfect uh search text
box ideal experience is talking to the
great agent who will uh put you in the
context of your problem uh understand
what you really need we'll know all the
neighborhoods so uh when we were
deciding to invest uh in this product uh
we thought that uh our mission is trying
to bridge the gap about experience that
user have uh when they use filters on
site an experience of talking to a human
who really understands your problem and
of course uh we had a strategic Vision
that if we don't start investing in llm
based and multimodel based search now in
couple of years we will be very much
behind the
race so
uh before we started building our Pro uh
product all searches were only filter
based and uh we already knew that
um we already knew that uh users are
doing a ton of things uh behind our
application for example uh if you like
certain uh visual aspect of interior
like wooden floor you would need to go
to each uh property and manually check
does it have wooden floor
no then uh if you want to check if your
apartment is close to supermarkets uh
you will need to go to the map and check
if it is close to the
supermarkets uh if you're looking for a
place to relocate with kids you uh you
want to find a good school uh you Al you
again you need to think about what
combination of filters will get you
there so uh we can add more and more
filters here but we uh we knew this is
not uh scalable way to solve the
problems uh and uh
what do we have
now uh this is really how our uh product
works uh despite we translated
everything to English from Portuguese
but this is live product uh I'm not sure
how visible this
is okay okay so uh user asks for
apartment in Copa cppa is a slang name
of kopa Cabana in Rio de
Janeiro uh price range between 10K and
20K with wooden floor and you can see
that
immediately uh the chat recognized uh
that uh location is Copa
Cabana selected filters are apartment
price range uh wooden floor as visual
aspect uh it understood the length so it
understood that Coppa is coopa Cabana
and behind the scenes it also understood
that uh with this price range uh this is
uh rent uh so person wants to rent
something and not buy a
house and if you are lucky with how
copilot understood you you can go to the
search and you can see that this first
beautiful apartment obviously has a
wooden floor uh the price range is
correct location is
correct so the product uh is doing what
we expected
what is hidden behind the scenes so it
fundamentally has a two big Parts uh
first one is data collector chat so we
need to know what to search so chat will
keep talking to a user until we get
enough data second is a search engine uh
which will retrieve the
information how architecture looks like
this is a first highlevel view into the
architecture so we take a plain te text
from the chat go to the chat Service
chat service has uh many functionalities
but uh basically it will extract filters
from the chat uh support the
conversation keep the user State as soon
as we are ready to search uh we will go
to the search service where hybrid
search will be
performed uh we will start with talking
about chat
uh let's zoom in a little bit more so
this is a chat solution uh another high
level architecture we will go even uh
lower so as you see we decided to go
with a router solution uh we have a
moderator at the beginning beginning and
all prompt injections and simply
unappropriate conversations are handled
here uh then we can send user to support
chatboard uh uh to the end of chatboard
but as we already know from the practice
most of users will go to the search flow
API uh the core part of the system so
let's Zoom even more to the search flow
API uh Julia will give you more interest
in details of this uh but uh basically
search flow has two big Parts one as I
mentioned before uh is filter extractor
the heart of our system converting the
plain text uh into Json with uh filters
and second is chat answering part uh
which helps to maintain the conversation
uh it is capable to do some location
suggestions
and keep the conversation going so over
to Julio to give you all me details of
the
solution thank you
T
hello so let's do a de dive a bit in the
futter extractor so this is an important
component of the search flow because
basically this is the
interface uh with the search service so
what we are doing here is we are taking
the user input and we are converting
into a Json and this Json will be later
translated into into an actual query
that will be consumed by the search
service so this future extractor is
actually we call it extractor but it's
actually updating information so we can
imagine that the user is already
interacting with the with the chat so we
already have some Json from pre previous
interactions so we receive a new input
and what we do is that we update this
Json so we can include new information
probably new filters we can update
existing filters or we can remove it
depending on what is coming from the Tex
input so this this is an actual complex
test because we have lots of different
Futures so we have 70 plus uh possible
different information the terministic
information that we can extract which is
a lot so here are some examples so for
instance the property type if the it's a
house or an apartment uh the business
context which is if is for rent or for
sale amenes and installations so all of
these informations uh are part of that
this Json that can have up to
71 different types of futters and we
also exract uh what we call a visual
element which is what we be using and
Lucas will talk about this later this is
what we'll be using to do the visual
multimodel search so basically we try to
extract something from the input uh that
we can use to do image search and this
is also being doing by this extractor
and here we have actually an individual
extraction with moderation as well so we
don't exract anything uh from this so we
we limit what we can extract and then we
join everything in a single
Jon so here's an example of a Jon of
course this can scale a lot depending on
how long is the conversation and
depending on what the user is asking but
we can see more or less what the Jon
looks like so we have things like
property type and the visual search
there we can see it's a list of strings
that will be used using for do the
multimodel search and we'll be seeing
this
later so here how the extractor how we
are handling this extraction so first we
take whatever the user already provided
which is the Json that represents the
user preferences for now and then we
take a new input so for instance the
user is actually updating the number of
bedrooms and he's asking for industry
style so what we do we do this in two
steps so we first do a
classification so this is basically a
multi-target classification that we are
doing for now with llms because we still
don't have enough data for training a
new model so for now we're doing this
with llm call so this is a multitarget
classification that is basically
classifying okay what Futures are in
this
input and then what we do is that we
pass uh this to the actual updator and
we say okay so those are the two filters
you must
update and this updator which is another
LM call will actually do the update so
in this example we'll be changing
bedrooms from three to two and we
updating the industry style so we do
this in this two
steps um and as T mentioned we also have
this chant answering part I will not
deep dive on this just a highlight here
but basically we can think about two
modules so one module has the entire
conversational history uh and this
module knows everything that this future
extractor API is doing so we we use this
modu to communicate the user whatever uh
related to Futures so this module knows
how to communicate changes in the future
and we also have a location module that
can handles with some limitations uh
location information
before we go into
search let me speak a bit about how do
we evaluate the entire chat which we
think it's an interesting topic so like
this is the the the entire architecture
right so basically those numbers is are
where we collect data so we collect data
from the input from the output of the
moderator we collect the classifications
from the router which is also classifier
we collect data in number four from the
entire search flow number five is
everything this the chat is answering to
the user and we also log the the prompts
in production so we double check that we
are actually using the appropriate
promps prompts in
production and depending on the task we
do different types of evaluation so we
always do offline and online evaluation
for all of the tasks here for all the
components for offline evaluation we
always use Golden data sets so we
manually produce golden data set to do
some off offline
evaluation and online evaluation of
course we're using production data and
sometimes we use class Co machine learn
evaluation sometimes we are using Jets
so we use llms to to do the evaluation
so how how is the difference here so for
objective and deterministics tasks such
as the router and the futter extractor
we are doing classical machine learn
evaluation and for more uh open-ended
questions and subjective tasks we are
using llms so the aspects is a nice
example of this because it's a list of
strings so it's hard to compare I mean
the ground truth and the prediction may
have different lengths and the text must
be different so this is hard to evaluate
it's easier to do something with a judge
for
example uh class machine learning as I
said we use offline and L we use both
online and offline depending on the task
and with class learning we can have more
Gran granular metrics while with the Jud
we are producing more generic metrics so
here's an example for the future
extractor so we can with class machine
learning we can have like like F1 score
so traditional metrics for every
individual uh
filter while with llm a J what we do is
that we do a more generic classific uh
evaluation into the input level so we
have an input for instance Santa cilia
two bedrooms Santa cilia by the way it's
a neighborhood in s Paulo so we classif
I we evaluate if the exraction as a
whole for this input is correct or
incorrect and how we are doing this with
the Jud so basically we follow these
four steps and the first one is the most
important one because basically what we
are doing we are trying to simplify the
original task so the original task here
is for instance this trctor right so we
first simplify this test to so we can
have an accurate uh evaluation with the
jet so it's correlated to our our actual
manual label data set then we do a
classical chain of thoughts and we
provide a grading
criteria and we ask the model to to do
to give a COR reason right so let me
give you an actual example so here again
Santa cilia which is a neighborhood uh
and two bedrooms so this is uh it's it's
not all this is just a part of what's
going to the judge okay but this is the
main component of the judge so the judge
is receiving okay this is the user
input this is the current user
preferences and what we what the model
is doing is he changed the location so
is this correct or not so we can see
that we somehow simplified the extractor
task and we basically said oh the
extractor action was to change the
location is this correct or not and then
the Jud can evaluate okay this is
correct because uh we changed the
location actually so the user had a
different location and we change it to
Santa Cecilia but the user asked for two
bedrooms and this is where already in
the filters so this is correct as well
there's nothing to do here so that's how
B more or less we we are using Alm as a
j so we simplify the task this score is
more generic but we can compute this
online once we fine tune The Prompt and
we know uh we our judge is good so this
is basically how we're doing the
evaluation and here is an overall
architecture of our
evaluation so we have important
component there which is uh golden data
sets so we take our production data and
we also include some Corner cases
manually include some Corner cases so we
can actually build golden data sets
which we use uh in offline evaluation
and cicd so every time we change
something we check if we are still with
uh the same level of accuracy before
deployment and we have the online
evaluation which takes production data
and run those types of evaluation that I
that I just mentioned so we can have
some error online and we have an
internal abstraction that's being used
uh by all of our systems which handles
both type of
evaluation okay so let me speak a bit
about things that we tried and what
worked best so once we were bu building
this entire architecture we began like
trusting a lot uh entirely on Al lams uh
instead of doing complex engineering
architectures and but at the end of the
day we arrive at a middle ground so we
ended up with the that architecture that
you saw which has a router it's has some
level of a state machine right combined
with llm
calls uh in terms of the futter
extractor we also try this like let's
try to do this filter update in a single
call with function calling and things
like that it was not that accurate
because we have a lot of filters so we
tried a very granular approach so
breaking down the text into chunks
trying to classify each individual chunk
and then doing the extraction it was not
also accurate then we evolve to this
twostep
approach and we what we are also doing
is that we are doing dividual uh
extraction for difficult components so
for instance amenity installations and
visual elements are two individual
complex components that we are handling
with individual LM calls and then we
merge everything together in this final
Json and finally in terms of
evaluation we tried in the very
beginning we we we didn't have
production data right so we didn't have
user data so how do you know if we're
doing well so we we tried building some
synthetic data sets with a LMS as well
and with some business rules but what
actually worked was to manually label
data and generate Corner cases so that's
how we began so generating manually
generating data sets and that help us to
like before doing any sort of uh actual
deployment and user test that allow us
to this is an actual an actual plot this
those are actual numbers so like in a
one month window we we were able to
somehow access our errors and improve
our extractor before doing any release
and before having any sort of data so we
we've done that with uh manual labeled
coding data
sets so that's it for the
chat so now what we will'll be seeing is
how we are actually doing the search so
how do we consume this Json and how do
we do this so this is what is going to
talk about yes thank you very much are
you listen the name to me okay all right
so let's talk a little bit about the
search part which I think it's uh
something that makes sense in this
conference right uh so let me just
quickly go back here to the product so
uh T showed a picture in the beginning
that showed the interface that we have
in the app uh so in theory where we are
right now is uh the user already said
what the user wants right so already use
like just text to reflect on what are
their preferences if everything got well
with the llm and there were no
hallucinations we should be able to do a
search with the preferences that the
user runs right so what we are going to
talk here is how this is actually
happening right how are we translating
this uh query which is coming from un
structure text and later passing through
an LM to generate the results that the
user actually wants to see but before
getting into how this is working right
now with the the whole chat uh
implementation I we'll just quickly go
back to how things worked before we had
a chat uh with all the LMS and all the
things going on right so in the app what
we have is uh essentially a very big
form where the user can select all the
things that they want in the house right
so the user can say whatever the price
they they're looking for whatever uh um
the features they're looking a house
whether uh you want you know a house
with a pool or without a pool and all
this so we have all this inside this
house features block that we showing
here but also there's a very important
information which is location right so
when you're looking for a house you
generally have uh a rough uh
understanding of where you want to live
so these two set of features are very
important and and they are uh actually
used as a first step uh in our retrieval
state so this information is actually
using for futuring out things so uh we
after this first stage of retrieval we
should be uh able to have a can a list
of cand houses there were then like and
this was I think clearly explained on
some of the preview presentations we
will be we'll be dealing with ranking
here so we have a two-step ranker we
have a light ranker that runs within
open search and we also have a heavy
ranker that is an ml model that is
considering user interaction uh uh
features and all these kinds of things
so then once we have this uh happening
we we then show the results to to the
user right now that we have a chat for
collecting data and it's very uh
important to mention here that now all
this information here including location
and house features aren't coming from
the chat itself uh we also added a new
dimension uh as jul mention which is the
visual preferences now so the user can
now freely describe what are the things
that they wanted to look into uh the
pictures of the houses right so we need
to update our our retrieval and ranking
system to reflect on this like how can
we use this information to uh uh help
the user and improve the search results
right so this is basically uh what we
want to do uh but just a quickly recall
uh this information that is coming from
the user is coming as text right so you
extract this as a list of strings
essentially and the information that we
want to compare to are House images
right so we have different kinds of uh
uh data here uh that we want to compare
so this was uh covered very well by by
Joe but I think it's uh very nice for us
to just quickly glance here uh
thankfully we have this multimodeling
Bings right so these are uh models and
ways of training models that allow you
to translate uh this instructure data
into a representation that allows you to
compare them right so in the end of the
day what we want is comparing texts with
images so we have here a a a
non-exhaustive list of models that are
open source you can actually uh uh use
them or you know recreate their uh
structure to generate those embeddings
and actually perform so this enters in
that um abstraction of py En coders
right so we can generate independent uh
embeddings they're going going to be
used for for this search so we are using
this this Technologies to support this
change right um but that's not enough
right so having uh the embeddings is one
very important uh First Step but we also
have to deal with how exactly we're
going to use this on our search so if
you recall correctly we have for a given
query we might have more than one uh
text right more than one sentence so in
this example that we showing here uh we
have a look a user that is looking for a
house with wooden floor big windows and
modern decoration so after all the llm
calls we end up with is a list of three
elements here which is first wooden
floor second big windows and modern
decoration and in our index our houses
might have uh many images right so if
you have a big house you're probably
going to have more images uh so all this
uh things need to somehow be compared in
such a way that we have in the end of
this comparison comparison a single
number that represents this matching
between the set of texts and the set of
images right so this is what I'm calling
here a scoring function uh so we need to
to solve this right so we need to uh
decide on how to to manage this this
kind of situation uh it's interesting to
see that the approach that we taking
here very similar to the patching of the
embeddings approach so uh essentially we
are doing uh is for each one of the
houses we uh perform a Parise C
similarity between all the textes and
all the images so we have one embedding
representation for each image one
embedding representation for each uh
text segment
and we perform the the cin similar
basically compute a m a distance Matrix
uh between this this set of embeddings
right once we have this uh we are
performing a uh basically a Max uh Max
operation uh griped by the visual
preference so for each one of those uh
uh text embeddings we are going to
choose uh the the image that actually
maximizes this similarity once we have
this we have a single score which we
calling here the image score that should
represent the matching between the
visual matching let's say let's put in
this way between the text and the the
the houses that we are looking for and
of course we need to do this for all the
houses so here we have house a and we
need to perform basically the same
operation for house B so once with this
is done uh we should end up with a
single uh score for D image but again if
you recall correctly from uh the the the
first picture that we showed from how
the system worked we don't have a single
score just for the image right so we
have other things we have a light ranker
we have a high heavy ranker so right now
this the all these scores are combined
so for each one of those uh houses we
are going to end up with a single score
and then we have the the usual just
ranking and topk uh uh selection so we
can actually show the results to the
user so this is basically how we are
handling uh images on our uh retrial
system uh again as Julia mentioned on
the chat like how are we evaluating this
like how is it's very important for us
to especially adding this new dimension
which is the the images how is our
system system behaving so similarly uh
this is still a search system right so
this is still a relevant system so we
still need to track all the metrics that
we usually track uh on such systems
right so given the search results and
given the user interaction after um the
existence of these results we can
compute relevance Matrix we can also
compute more kind of business conversion
Matrix in this case for example at konar
we want to know whether a search uh
somehow was connected to a visit or if
it was connected to a new contract or
something like this so this um measures
the overall health of the of the system
uh but it's important especially now
that we are adding this this new this
new layer there no multimodality to the
whole system which is being able to
explain a little bit and see if the
experience that we showing to the user
uh is actually reflecting the images so
in a in a very similar way uh that we
did on the chat we can also use llms as
a judge to actually see and evaluate if
the results of the search that we uh
given to the users make sense so in this
case specifically given a search result
and a user query we just basically ask
those multimodel llms whether the
results address the user requirements of
course this is something that we have to
do like you have to kind of see whether
it makes sense or not because uh in some
cases for example we notice some some
bugs in our models that they couldn't
correctly represent some kinds of uh
visual uh elements so having this uh
llms being able to uh automatically
evaluate the results allow you to
actually pick up those those specific
issues earlier so this is something that
we are actually improving a little bit
and trying to explore whether uh uh this
is going to be very helpful uh in a
production uh setting right uh so just
to summarize a little bit of the things
and some of the learnings that we had
and things that we were thinking about
the in terms of improvements for the
system in in the future
uh we actually had to uh uh during the
whole process uh think a lot about like
performance and how we would deal with
all those embedding so we have many
houses we have many images for houses so
we actually had to think about how to
per improve the performance for this
whole system so one of the approaches
that we took were actually very similar
to the clustering BL based one that Joe
mentioned we actually perform a
clustering and select images that
represent those clusters and just index
those images so instead instead of
having all the images that might be
representing the same visual uh aspects
we actually uh uh cluster them and just
uh pick those representative examples to
index and perform the actual search on
this so this was a very important thing
uh for the for the development um we
also tested different similarity
aggregation strategies so right now if
you recall we are performing the sum of
Max we also tried other combinations so
you also tried averaging the sums
averaging the maximums uh maximum Max of
the Maxes and each one of them have have
different consequences in terms of the
experience that you show to the user it
it is even possible that you might have
different strategies for different users
this is something that we discussed
before like uh uh some users are looking
specifically for one visual aspect and
they think that this is very important
so depending on the aggregation strategy
that you're using uh you might end up
with a different result with different
quality for different users uh in terms
of future uh I think we talked a little
bit about here uh about hybrid search
right now we just performing mostly
Vector search for the image and you know
reranking uh but we also understand that
it's possible that you know pm25 can be
helpful if we are able to create good
descriptions of those houses so let's
say we can use for example
gp4 or any other good llm for generating
texts and very detailed descriptions we
could probably be using you know more
traditional full Tex you know lexo
search to um enhance those results
together with the with the house um
images uh Beyond this uh talking a
little bit about the the granularity
levels right now we we're looking mainly
at Image level embeddings uh but we
understand that if we could have for
example a representation that uh gave us
um most of the information encoded in a
single embedding for the whole house
this would also help uh Us in terms of
performance of the search and and maybe
well even even in and some other metrics
uh another thing that is also in our
mind and we are actually working
actively on this is on our heavy ranker
stage we should probably in the future
consider image features as well or at
least some kind of aggregation of those
image features right now the um the
ranker doesn't consider image features
so you might have some incompatibility
right you might have for example a a
model that is ranking images uh based on
similarity and then you have a ranker
that actually kind of makes it kind of a
mess in terms of the ranks that they
generate regarding the images right so
having a ranker that reflects on the on
the image features is also something
that could be very important uh and
finally one of the downsides of the
approach that we're taking which is
using images mainly for ranking is that
we are not able to um filter out results
that are not matching this so it's very
hard to define a matching when you're
dealing with in batting because you
basically you need to pick a threshold
right and picking thresholds is really
hard like it's something that is it's a
a very hard task especially on this on
this model so uh we are still kind of
exploring ways of how how we should be
doing this but it would be really nice
if a user said okay um I'm looking for a
a I don't know a green pool and if we
don't have a green pool we actually
don't show any results but right now the
experience is not exactly this because
we can't remove Things based on on the
embedding similarity just uh uh without
a treshold right so I think this uh
wraps up uh the search part uh I hope I
wasn't too fast or too low uh but I I I
wanted to use this opportunity to
actually thank the team like this uh is
a huge project like this is something
that we are working for uh quite some
time here at the company and it's we are
just here representing uh you know a
pool of very brilliant Engineers PMS
designers uh data scientists so uh I
like to use this opportunity to thank
the team and of course you guys uh
because this was a very interesting
project to work on and if you uh are you
interested in the challenges we are also
actually hiring so uh let me know like
you can you know talk to us uh it would
be very welcome uh uh having you know
people with lots of good knowledge about
search and relevance so feel free to
reach out to us and I think that's it
for
now thank you do we have any questions
here in the room yeah
all thanks for the talk that was great
um wonderful case study so um when
you've got your chatbot obviously
that'ss letting the user specify lots of
filters how do you avoid if they ask a
very complex question or take it all the
way down the rabbit holes they've given
you loads of filters and that's reduce
the possible results set to the point
where there's basically nothing matching
their query and obviously then they're
going to think your search is broken how
do you deal with that I will I will take
this yes that's actually one of the
first problems we decided to tackle uh
after uh first release uh so we want to
extend this to guided search and make a
actually leverage recommendations to
make a suggestion uh how to reduce
either filter set or extend uh filters
maybe to multiple locations or uh like
uh play with the price so actually we uh
we're preparing to release this guided
search feature that will navigate users
to nonzero search
results we have one online question um
it's about guard rails did you implement
or how did you implement guard rails in
your chatbot how do you deal with
security and possible abuse of your
users by the chatbot is there anything
you've done there yes I can take this
one so yes we have sepal layers of bar
rails actually so we have the providers
but bar rails of course we also use it
but this is this is the main guard rail
we have which is this custom moderator
and we have another one inside the
search flow that is moderating what goes
into the image search so basically those
are also based on llms and what we do is
that we try to avoid prompt in injection
harmful content um and we do
so every single user input goes into
this gu rail every time and we call a
second gu rail inside the the future
extractor which is to moderate uh the
visual components because those are also
open uh text so we we need to block uh
some of this text so we it doesn't go
into the the image
search I have a question more about the
ux part of it uh so traditionally I find
that uh classified ads websites have
tried uh full teex search a number of
times but users stick to the filters to
the dropboxes uh it's such an
established domain and we use those
filters even in print in the old times
um so what's the nature of the question
that they really want to have answered
by the chatbot and how much adaption is
there yeah I will take this one this is
actually very good question and uh we
see this is partially happening with our
users uh what we see is the promise like
what makes uh the difference for users
is ability to solve problems they are
not able to solve with filters and uh
this is like this ability uh to search
for visual aspects uh like in any form
that works for them this is both coming
from ux researches and from actual
results showing that uh if user start
using this visual filters uh actually
the business metrix uh going up and
currently what our product management
team is working is like educating users
what are the benefits for them to start
talking to us
like i' like to squeeze one in from
online again um uh the question is what
kind of annotation or lab labeling tools
did you use to create your golden data
set anything self-developed or what did
you use for that yeah we internally we
actually use label studio uh which is an
open source too for I think they have a
paid version as well it's a service but
uh we have a deployment uh in house uh
in which we uh basically created a
process there to annotate it's a very
complex process because we have 71 uh
Futures and we notice that this plays a
very important role in evaluation
because at least in the first times uh
uh we noticed that most of the time
we're actually evaluating the annotator
and not the the the the tool itself
because there's so many annotation
errors it's it's so hard to to do this
that having a tool that kind of
streamlines and help as much as possible
the annotator doing this uh uh ined up
and then we choose this this specific
tool which is Lio Studio okay I think
we're at time sorry maybe we can you can
talk to Tana Julio and Lucas during the
break we have a 50-minute break but
first thanks uh again everyone